How has managing your mental health and making
sure that you manage your stress in your positions,
but then also through that kind of
work-life balance dynamic that you just talked about?
So I think you have to
have more than one focus in life.
So my rhythm is I get
up at 4.30 in the morning.
I'm in the gym by 5.
I work out generally seven days a week.
Some weeks I work out six, but mostly it's seven.
Some days I do a couple workouts.
Because to me, that allows me to mind space.
It's me, my myself.
It's me shooting for my goals in that area.
And then I also have hobbies.
I play golf.
Not very well, but I do like to play golf.
I sail.
I love to sail.
I love to hike.
I love to road bike.
And so to me, all those are
ways to get away from the office.
And when Abraham Lincoln had four hours
to chop down a tree, he said,
spend the first three sharpening the axe.
And so to me, those other
things that you do sharpen the axe.